# **BAYU MAULANA IKHSAN**

085713823408 | bayu.maulanaikhsan123@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/bayumaulanaikhsan/

Magelang, Jawa Tengah

I am website developer with 2 years of experience in website development, using Laravel for developing a website and web applications. I am a graduate of AMIKOM Yogyakarta University majoring in Information Systems. I have the ability to program using Scrum, Javascript, Jquery, PHP, laravel, Codeigniter, MYSQL, and Git. Have good analytical and communication skills and be able to work individually or in a team.

### Work Experiences

### BKAD Kabupaten Sleman - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - Present

Programmer

- Developing and overcoming user problems of Sistem Informasi Keuangan Daerah (SIKD) and Sistem Pengajuan Surat Rekening (SPSR) related to applicable policies of Sleman including, troubleshooting, disaster recovery planning & execution.
- Carry out other duties related to the Sistem Informasi Keuangan Daerah (SIKD), Sistem Pengajuan Surat Rekening (SPSR), and related systems.
- Developing Sistem Informasi Manajemen Barang dan Jasa (SIMBAJA) related to policies in force in Sleman with microservices.

#### PT Mandala Dwipantara Proteksi - Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

Software Engineer

- Developing and overcoming user problems of NRE-CORE related to applicable policies of PT. Reasuransi Nasional Indonesia including, troubleshooting, disaster recovery planning & execution.
- · Meeting and discussing program design with clients.

### PT. Time Excelindo - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

Internship Web Programmer

- · Contribute to the development of the HR TOOLS website
- Develop features in HR TOOLS, including: fixing bugs, developing attendance with shifts and distances, applying for leave and overtime permits, and developing employee assessments

### PT Zeniora Edukasi Teknologi - Surabaya, Indonesia

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021

Internship Back End Developer

- Contribute to the management of the Zeniora website
- · Participate in the process of creating a new menu in the rest api section

## **Education Level**

### AMIKOM University Yogyakarta - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Aug 2018 - Feb 2022

Bachelor Degree in Information Systems, 3.72/4.00

### Organisational Experience

### Himpunan Mahasiswa Program Studi Manajemen Informatika dan Sistem Informasi - Yogyakarta

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022

Vice Chairman

- Contribute to organization management
- Participate in the committee recruitment process
- · Responsible for making activity reports

### Himpunan Mahasiswa Program Studi Manajemen Informatika dan Sistem Informasi - Yogyakarta,

Aug 2019 - Jan 2021

Indonesia

Head of Internal Department

- Ensure harmonious relations between members
- · Organize and ensure daily management activities
- · Contribute in the preparation of organizational activities
- Ensure that every member contributes to activities

### Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Hard Skills: HTML, CSS, PHP (Laravel, Codelgneter), Javascript, Jquery, MYSQL, and Git
- Portfolio: https://portfolio-bayumaul.vercel.app/
- •